One of those changes, of course, Malcolm Marks missing now through injury.
So Bongi and Banami comes in at hookup.
A couple of heavy bookends with him in the shape of Franz Malhaber and Stephen Kitzoff.
Kitzoff on his way to Ireland, Irish side Ulster after the Rugby World Cup.
An experienced second row, coming up for 200 counts between them.
It's the best someone you just hate to play against.
And the workhorse alongside him, Franco Moster.
The back row of Visa, Dutoy and Khaleesi.
Visa, a ferocious carrier.
Dutoy, he was just everywhere in round one.
He even got a try for himself.
And Khaleesi, the absolute poster boy of Rugby and its values.
9-10, the Everite catching fast to clerk.
And he'll be serving Marnie Le Bois, publicly backed by a skipper recently.
He's no looking game one.
Possibly my favourite moment of the World Cup so far.
Damien Diolendi and Jesse Creel.
Diolendi used to play for Ireland in Munster.
So he'll be well aware of what's to come for him.
And the back three, Olympian Colby on one wing.
Iron set on the other.
The Bulls speedster.
One of the best finishes in World Rugby.
And Willemstad, the powerful yet graceful man in the 15th shirt.
Coming as a six-stage grand slam winners,
they'd love to be champs of Europe and the world.
It's an all-enster front row.
We've got Andrew Porter, Ronan Kelher and Ty Gvallong.
The Rugby World Rugby Dream Team, two years in a row.
He's up for a great battle with Kitt's off,
as he'll face down in him in the scrum.
The Munster man, Ty Burn, lines up alongside James Ryan.
He's captain of his country, but it's his leadership at the line-out time,
which could be crucial against South Africa.
And talking about leadership.
Peter Marnie led Munster to a URC title this year.
He goes out alongside Ireland's players for the year for 2023.
Kaelin Doris and Josh van der Flier.
9-10, the ever-exciting Pacey, Jamie Gibson-Park.
And then fly-half, Johnny Sexton,
who has 1,090 points to his name.
World record.
A centre partnership by Andy Akie and Gary Ringrose.
They have 18 out of 22 wins,
when those two have played alongside each other.
And the big boot, James Lowe and the wing.
Kaelin continues to make the 15th in Jersey's own.
And Mack Hansen at 14, who said,
it's probably everything you dream of growing up playing in games like this.
And then Dan Sheehan will make his rugby World Cup debut,
if he comes up for the bench.
Locking horns with the spring box.
At start to France.
South Africa have fond memories from watching those
that can't be fooled in winning the rugby World Cup.
Number one in the world, Ireland.
Take on the defending champion, South Africa.
It's a pull-beam match, which could easily be
as tight as a facelift.
Welcome to start to France.
Straight away, it's Simon Villosa into the fray.
He's up-ended.
South Africa in their white jersey.
Their third strip of this rugby World Cup.
Fuck the clock, looking to go wide early on.
And it's been spilt on that far side.
But in the hole of the last rugby World Cup.
To the front they go.
Tideburn, Clon Pinch.
That's Hoofdownfield.
By Colby, not out.
Left behind from Mack Hansen.
Always going backwards in the touch.
Happy there, Jamee.
And South Africa go quickly.
Fuck the clock.
Spots a bit of space.
And it's an awkward bounce, but it's good for South Africa.
Curly Aronson has it, look out.
Creel's on the inside.
Big Jesse Creel into the 22.
And the clean-up from Diolendi.
Through the legs it goes.
Seven-style play there from Fuff the clock.
Game back on, Jasper Visser.
South Africa now, their chance to attack.
Big step, Damien Villosa.
Does well inside the 20s.
Running the box, turns.
The flags go up.
South Africa have the opening points in this game.
South Africa won that one.
There last time.
They've beaten the Irish.
Gibson Park rolls it backwards.
Aki again, burst to the line.
Bundy Aki looking to go over the half-way line.
Aki is a sensation in this game.
Into the 22 for Ireland.
Gibson Park.
So a bunch of white jerseys flying up on the right-hand side.
Decided to take contact.
Numbers to the left.
Porter.
For Ireland.
Can they capitalise on their break by Bundy Aki?
He carries again.
Delayed ball.
You know, Manny's there.
Much better from this Irish side.
A second carry again from Andrew Porter.
David in 2017.
Sexton crunched as he gives the inside ball to James Lowe.
Porter for the third time.
The hits keep coming.
Gibson Park shifts up to the right as Ireland
trying to make some progress here in the 22.
Sexton.
Just a wall away jerseys with Datoi again.
Behind the back ball.
And a lock.
Josh Vanda for the up.
Sexton.
Over the top he goes.
Bundy Aki yet again.
Beautiful ball to Lowe on the inside.
Needs help.
There's Mosta Zolabra.
And a varnish for the Irish side.
Porter.
Nice dummy from the front row forward from Lenster.
A free play here for the Irish side with advantage.
Gibson Park.
Still got a pin away advantage.
Across they'll go.
The cross kick from Henshaw.
And Ireland will come back.
You're always in contact.
The Techler goes to ground.
No clear release.
That is great news for the Irish side.
They crowd love that they kick for the corner.
Because here comes Callaghan out to the front.
Vanda Flair peels around.
It's a bet hasn't.
Bundy Aki.
Their most dangerous runner tonight.
Still the Irish wave comes.
At South Africa.
Gibson Park to the right.
Forward quickly regathering themselves for the next wave.
Peter Omani.
Gibson Park.
Looks both ways.
Again it's Vanda Flair.
Ireland inching their way closer to the spring box.
Beautiful play.
Sexton throws a dummy.
He gets so close to Johnny Sexton.
There it is.
He's behind.
To the right.
No the numbers there.
Ireland will score.
And they put it down.
Mac Hansen.
Rocks one in for the Irish.
And the crowd erupts.
It's not the Braals.
That's a beautiful bit of play.
Johnny Sexton gets so close.
The scramble from South Africa.
And it goes wide into the hands of the Moustachio at Mac Hansen.
Who gets over for Ireland's first score.
Seven points.
If Sexton can put this one over.
What a moment for Mac Hansen.
Born and bred in Canberra Australia.
He played super rugby for the Brumbies.
Too many other titles to list right now.
He lines up the extra two to Sexton.
It's straight through the middle.
It's Ireland's seven.
South Africa three.
Just to skip out.
Just with this up.
Gibson Park.
Sexton quick hands.
The Oxford Bull is there.
James Ryan.
Catters forward.
Ireland.
Peter Stepp, the tour has it.
Difficult pass for Khaleesi to take.
Almost.
My advantage, it's halftime.
Ireland coming through here.
And that is the first 40 minutes gone.
They're insane.
Denny North of Paris.
It's the pool B-battle at the 2023 Rugby World Cup.
When you would be close and it is.
A halftime score.
Sees Ireland leads.
South Africa seven three.
Looks on from Ireland.
You're watching the second half between Ireland
and South Africa from starting start to France
at the 2023 Rugby World Cup.
Ireland on the left, lead seven three
against South Africa.
Andy Aki with a take.
Welcome to you for the thrilling pool B matchup.
Pitch side net.
You need to use the right side.
Here comes Vissa for South Africa.
Straight away.
A quick pinch.
Mosted.
Henry.
To the line for the spring box.
On the floor.
Aki.
Comes in down to the halfway line.
For the Irish side.
Cut her again.
Takes some kits off.
Khaleesi comes in.
Hams the pill.
Stays with...
What's to the ball?
The men in green.
Use it!
He takes them to the right inside.
He lets his forwards attack a bit more.
Penalty.
South Africa.
One up.
From inside.
He's off.
Fuff the clack.
As if the upright.
It's come bouncing back.
And flying up there was Cheslin Colby
for South Africa.
Somehow the spring box have it.
Kill goes to the right.
And Benubbi's there.
This may work out better for the spring box
if they do score a try.
Jasper Vissa.
Crunches forward.
The clack finds.
It's a bit.
Who's picked up.
That is a highlight rail for social media.
Yeah, then it's a bit.
Has been thrown out of the party.
Crouch.
Fuff the bind.
Six.
Ever up.
Vantage.
Lucy claps.
Ever.
Vantage for South Africa
with four of the Bum Squad members on the field.
The Elendi beautiful ball.
On the outside.
South Africa will power over.
Cheslin Colby.
What a try.
Forget low-chilling.
He's electric 24-7.
And it was Marnie LaBotte
that delivered the goods.
Cheslin Colby, the Olympian.
He's magic in open space.
And there was plenty of it down in this touchline.
The only easier run in Zilheim.
The clock ticks.
Five seconds to take the kick.
Just pulls it to the left-hand side.
And the same's continuing here.
This is Cool Beat.
Number one and two side in the world.
Happens to collide here.
It's penalty to Ireland.
Sexton is a smooth operator.
And Ireland go back into lead.
And half.
The half-minute rugby.
The forwards.
And the spring box.
Call one back.
Pushing straight.
Oh, they're not staying straight.
The red numbers getting very low.
As Marnie LaBotte looks on.
Unsuccessful.
Has come onto the field.
The big changes are both sides.
Who can finish off strongly?
Here comes Cochess Smith.
He's not scared.
No, wait, wait.
First touch.
He can be the oldest test.
Debbie Tuntin, South African history.
His first cap is nearly 36 years old.
The 31-year-old.
Bangs it downfield.
And misses.
Here we go.
As the world watches.
Pell the Ireland.
You can hear the roar.
Point lead.
Fally has his name in the box.
It's 13 points to rate.
Ireland leads South Africa.
Mourning towards the Thailand.
Lenny's in there as well.
Tideburn.
The Irish defender on the side.
The defender's superbly.
They're trying to dig us out.
It's there.
Ireland.
Have done it.
The number one team in the world.
Irish stars are smiling tonight.
They've taken one step closer
to their rugby world cup dream.
They're beating the spring box.
It's been an extraordinary evening in Paris.
There'll be tears.
There'll be celebrations.
80,000 fans.
Millions around the world.